Guide to the Architectural and Engineering Services, Yale University, Records Concerning Capital Maintenance
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Architectural and Engineering Services, Yale University, records concerning capital maintenance
1967-1987
RU 196
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1
The records consist of administrative files, maintained by Ken Borst, documenting cost estimates for Yale building projects.
Yale University. Architectural and Engineering Services
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-A (YRG 46-A), Records and materials broadly documenting Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by subject or building project.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of administrative files, maintained by Ken Borst, documenting cost estimates for Yale building projects.
Campus planning; College buildings -- Design and construction; College buildings -- Maintenance and repair; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Finance; Yale University. Architectural and Engineering Services
- Cost estimates for Yale buildings, 1967-1987; Accession 1991-A-121
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
  - Sterling Library - Cross Campus Cost Breakdown, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mellon, 1971 September 24 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mellon Estimate by Architect, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - G. A. Fuller Estimate - Fire Loss
    - Art and Architecture Building, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mellon, 1972 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Garvan Collection, 1970 October 16 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Laboratory for Surgery, Obstetrics, and Gynecology (L.S.O.G.)
    - 1972 Mar 7 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mellon Estimate, 1970 October 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Culinary Institute - Angell Hall Estimate, 1970-1987 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Laboratory for Surgery, Obstetrics, and Gynecology III
    - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 1967-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)